# **Leonardo Rodriguez**

Remote Web3 dApp Developer

### **Contact Info**

Email: leo@fullstackleo.net Mobile Phone: +1 512 312 8481 Location: Eagle Pass, Texas, USA



## **Summary**

I'm a high-energy and knowledge thirsty **Remote Web3 dApp Developer** with 15 years of experience in fullstack development, business management, and creative direction. I am now building Web3 dApps using tech like Solidity, Hardhat, Foundry, and EVM chains (Ethereum, Polygon, BSC). Frontend with React/Next.js, backend with Node.js/TypeScript. I'm skilled with ERC-20/721/1155, Metamask, WalletConnect, The Graph, IPFS, and cross-chain tools. Secure, gas-efficient, end-to-end dApp development is at your service.

I speak native English and Spanish. 🚹 🥌

### **Portfolios**

- Full Stack Dev: https://fullstackleo.net
- Web Dev, Design, Writing: https://idealeo.net
- GitHub: https://github.com/fullstackleo777

#### Skills

- **Deployment:** Linux (Ubuntu, CentOS, RHEL), AWS, GCP, Windows Azure, Docker, Podman, CI/CD
- Database: MySQL, NoSQL, SQLite, MariaDB, PostgreSQL, Database Visualizers
- 🧠 Back End: Linux, Bash Scripting, Cron Jobs, SSH, Node.js, PHP, Python, REST API, Autho
- Front End: XML, HTML, CSS/SCSS/SASS, Javascript, Organic SEO, Frameworks (Vue.js, Svelte, React.js)
- Open Source Software: Server (Apache, NGINX, Lighttpd, ffmpeg), Productivity (OpenOffice, LibreOffice)
- Creative Software: Adobe (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Premiere Pro), Open Source (Inkscape, Gimp)
- 🔐 Server Security: Firewalled, SSL/TLS, Fail2Ban, SSH Keys, Argon2, IP White/Blacklisting
- 🔑 DNS Security: DNSSEC, DDOS Protection, Secure Cache, DNS Proxy, DNS Firewall
- 👚 Content Management Systems: HubSpot, Wordpress, Wix, Squarespace, Drupal
- 💰 eCommerce Platforms: WP WooCommerce, Magento CE, Shopify, Thirty Bees, Wix, Squarespace
- X Dev Tooling: GIT (GitHub, GitLab, GiTea), VSCodium, VSCode, Vim, Nano, DIFF, Chrome DevTools
- Project Management: Agile, Scrum, Lean, BPM



#### **Work Experience**

### Remote Freelance Full Stack Developer at Freelance from January 2016 to December 2024

Since the tech industry is very unpredictable, when I don't have a full time job, I work as a freelancer. In this position, I planned/built/maintained full stack development projects (LAMP, MERN, Wordpress, Shopify), designed brand identities using Photoshop/Illustrator/GIMP/Inkscape, developed for web/mobile using HTML/CSS/SASS/Javascript/Node.js/Vue.js/VSCodium/PHP, designed custom print projects, managed business (accounting, sales, client relations), and led teams of freelancer talent to successful project completion.

Remote QA Specialist and Web Developer at Education Strategy Consulting, INC. from June 2021 to November 2023 Office Location: Charlottesville, Virginia | Phone: +1 434 961 2584 | Website: https://escmatrix.com

In this role, I scrutinized the company's Java/R/Podman/Node.js/HTML/CSS/SASS/Javascript/PostgreSQL web development process, QA tested big data web apps on varied environments (AWS, Localhost, BrowserStack), unit tested ESC's proprietary development framework, wrote technical documentation, kept track of ongoing issues/bugs across multiple projects, QA tested big data renders via automated tests, and QA tested data manually on LibreOfficeCalc/WebApp.

### Full Stack Developer at PetroPages, INC. from July 2018 to April 2021

Office Location: Webster, TX | Phone: +1 281 316 0353 | Website: https://petropages.com

Onsite, I worked on enterprise & medium business scale projects, secured servers (Linux, Ubuntu, CentOS, Azure, AWS, GCP), encrypted databases (MySQL, MariaDB), shielded REST API endpoints, hardened/encrypted/sanitized/speed-optimized digital products (LetsEncrypt, Fail2Ban, and more!), executed the company-wide switch to GIT version control with CI/CD along with Adrian (CTO), converted front-end mockup designs into HTML/CSS/JavaScript/PHP/Wordpress, executed architecture updates/upgrades (LAMP, GCP, AWS, Azure), crafted HubSpot marketing campaigns, and maintained/troubleshooted/debugged back-end programming (PHP and .NET).

# Business Manager at SignDepotATX from December 2015 to January 2017

Office Location: Austin, TX | Phone: +1 512 219 8000 | Website: https://signdepotatx.com

I began as a graphic designer setting up print files but was promoted to business manager once I started talking to clients/prospects and increasing sales volume. As manager, I managed interns/designers/production/shop workflows, created sales training manuals with Fernando which increased sales, maintained vendor/client relations, designed signage/branding/marketing material using Photoshop/Illustrator, executed organic SEO camapaigns on Magento Store, sent out mass communications using MailChimp, and created successful marketing campaigns.

Creative Director at Image Master Group - A Division of XL Sales & Marketing, LLC. from February 2012 to November 2015 Office Location: Austin, TX | Phone: +1 512 365 0135 | Website: https://imagemastergroup.com

Along with Jose (CEO), I designed company catalogs, created sales presentations for the sales team, created digital graphics for web use, art directed creative marketing campaigns, designed marketing material/promo videos/TV ads/social media imagery/signage/ambient event imagery using Photoshop/Illustrator/Premiere/Sparkle, developed company website using Wix, pushed mass communications via Constant Contact, and developed brochure websites for clientele using Notepad++/HTML/CSS/JavaScript/PHP/WHM with cPanel hosting.

#### Education

Bachelor's of Science in Graphic & Web Design Program from The Art Institute in Austin, TX from August 2010 to July 2014